<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MovieApp</string>
    <string name="imageDescription_of_movie">Image of the movie Queens Gambit.</string>
    <string name="creators">Creators:</string>
    <string name="actors">Actors:</string>
    <string name="storyTitle">Story</string>
    <string name="description">The Queens Gambit follows the life of an orphan chess prodigy, Elizabeth Harmon, during her quest to become the world\'s greatest chess player while struggling with emotional problems and drug and alcohol dependency. The title of the series refers to a chess opening of the same name. The story begins in the mid-1950s and proceeds into the 1960s.[4]

The story begins in Lexington, Kentucky, where a nine-year-old Beth, having lost her mother in a car crash, is taken to an orphanage where she is taught chess by the building\'s custodian, Mr. Shaibel. As was common during the 1950s, the orphanage dispenses daily tranquilizer pills to the girls,[5][6] which turns into an addiction for Beth. She quickly becomes a strong chess player due to her visualization skills, which are enhanced by the tranquilizers. A few years later, Beth is adopted by Alma Wheatley and her husband from Lexington. As she adjusts to her new home, Beth enters a chess tournament and wins despite having no prior experience in competitive chess. She develops friendships with several people, including former Kentucky State Champion Harry Beltik, United States National Champion Benny Watts, and journalist and fellow player D.L. Townes. As Beth rises to the top of the chess world and reaps the financial benefits of her success, her drug and alcohol dependency becomes worse.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="menu_item_watchlist">To Watchlist</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_movieapp">Welcome to MovieApp!</string>
    <string name="see_detail">SEE DETAIL</string>
    <string name="marvelsDescription">
        Loki, der Halbbruder des Donnergottes Thor, will die Erde unterjochen. Um der Menschheit diese Zukunft zu ersparen, ruft Nick Fury, Chef der geheimen Regierungsbehörde und Friedensorganisation S.H.I.E.L.D., die größten Helden der Welt zusammen. Captain America wird aus seinem jahrzehntelangen Schlaf geweckt und schließlich greift Fury zudem auf die Dienste des egozentrischen Tony Stark, aka Iron Man, zurück. Auch der Wissenschaftler Dr. Bruce Banner wird ins Team gelockt.
    </string>
    <string name="imitationDescription">
        Der britische Geheimdienst engagiert im Zweiten Weltkrieg den Mathematiker Alan Turing für eine heikle Mission: Er soll mit seinem Team den Enigma-Geheimcode der deutschen Wehrmacht entschlüsseln. Mit seiner komplexen Entschlüsselungsmaschine gelingt dem Genie der Durchbruch. Turing wird zum gefeierten Star. Doch auch er hat ein Geheimnis, das nicht in die falschen Ohren gelangen darf: Er ist homosexuell. 1952 wird dem ehemaligen Helden dieses Vergehen zum Verhängnis.
    </string>
    <string name="wolfDescription">
        Mit Anfang 20 gründet der Aktienhändler Jordan Belfort seine eigene Firma, die schnell zum großen Erfolg wird. Er wird zum Multimillionär und Star an der New Yorker Börse, der von allen nur Wolf of Wall Street genannt wird. Jordan genießt sein ausschweifendes Luxusleben in vollen Zügen und fühlt sich unbesiegbar. Seine unstillbare Gier nach mehr Geld bringt ihn schließlich dazu, sich gemeinsam mit seinen Freunden auf illegale Geschäfte einzulassen. Doch das FBI ist ihm bald auf den Fersen.
    </string>
    <string name="watchlist">My Watchlist</string>
</resources>